Arturo Jara

UX-UI Designer

I am a graduate of the communication sciences career, but I changed to the design and front end area until I got to UX.

I decided to switch to this profession to create new experiences for all kinds of people and solve problems of daily life in a suitable way for everyone.



CONTACT

- +52-646-226-84-58
- arturojara1994@gmail.com
- behance/arturojara
- instagram.com/arturojaracreativo

EDUCATION

2012-2017 • Licienciado en Ciencias de la comunicación Universidad Autónoma de Baja California

2020-2020 • Foundations of User Experience (UX) Design
Google Certificate UX Design

SKILLS

Wordpress

HTML CSS y JS

Tailwind

Bulma

IOS, Android

Ux Design

Design Systems

REACT (Layout)

EXPERIENCE

2021- 2022 • UX Designer

Rivka Development

UX-UI design in user tests, app testing, HTML layout. CSS, JS, REACT, ANGULAR, FIGMA ADOVBE XD and ILLUSTRATOR

2020-2021 • UX Designer

Freelance

I do research work on my own and create web pages for clients with the entire Design Thinking process, making mock ups, wireframes, user flows, usability tests, etc.

Until now I have participated in 3 projects on my own that are in my portfolio, Fedecoop, Tap o meter and IIO.

2017-2020 • Web Designer

Dolly Agencia

Design of mock ups in Adobe XD and flyers for advertising campaigns, in addition to layout in HTML, CSS, JS, REACT JS, I also used GIT.